Finding Aid for Marshall L. Cook and William R. Cook papers, 1880-1945
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Marshall L. Cook and William R. Cook papers 1880-1945
Cook, Marshall L., 1858-1955.
851174 Aa 2
Editor and publisher, with his brother, William Randolph Cook, of the Hastings Banner in Hastings, Michigan. Correspondence, 1893-1941, relating to operations of their paper and other business enterprises, including material concerning Republican politics, the temperance movement, their activities and interest in the Rotary Club, the Salvation Army, and the Young Men's Christian Association.
6 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Richard M. Cook (donor no. 3240 ) and came to the library in multiple accessions.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Marshall L. Cook was born August 12, 1858 in Prairieville Township, Barry County, Michigan. After attending Albion College, he returned to Hastings, Michigan where he purchased an interest in the Hastings Banner newspaper around 1880. In 1889, his brother William R. Cook was able to buy out one of the newspapers owners and from that time the two brothers operated the newspaper together.
William R. Cook was born January 28, 1866. He attended the University of Michigan for two years, then returned to Hastings where he intended to study law. For reasons of health, he was forced to abandon these plans and instead purchased an interest in the local newspaper and printing business which he operated with his brother.
The two brothers were active in civic, professional, and political affairs. William R. Cook was long-time treasurer of the Michigan Press Association and secretary of the Hastings Rotary Club. Marshall L. Cook was president of the Michigan Republican Editors Association.
The collection has been arranged into three series: Correspondence; Hasting Rotary Club; and Miscellaneous. The correspondence has been arranged chronologically with separate folders when needed for specific kinds of activities of the two brothers: political, business, church activities, and other professional responsibilities.
Subjects:
Barry County (Mich.); Cook, Marshall L., 1858-1955.; United States. Congress--Elections, 1896.; Elections--Michigan--1896.; Elections--Michigan--1900.; Elections--Michigan--1902.; Elections--Michigan--1908.; Presidents--United States--Election--1908.; Hastings (Mich.); Hastings banner.; American newspapers--Michigan--Hastings.; Prohibition--Michigan.; Republican Party (Mich.); Hastings Rotary Club (Hastings, Mich.); Salvation Army.; Temperance--Michigan--Hastings.; Presidents--United States--Election--1916.; Elections--Michigan--1910.; Elections--Michigan--1912.; Elections--Michigan--1914.; Elections--Michigan--1916.; United States. Congress--Elections, 1910.; United States--Politics and government--1865-1900.; Michigan--Politics and government--1877-1898.; United States--Politics and government--1901-1953.; Michigan--Politics and government--1899-1916.; Michigan--Politics and government--1917-1921.; World War, 1914-1918.; Young Men's Christian Associations.; Michigan--Politics and government--1837-1950.
Contributors:
Aitken, David Demerest, 1853-1930.; American Press Association.; American Protective Tariff League.; Anti-Saloon League of Michigan.; Bliss, Aaron Thomas, 1837-1906.; Blodgett, John Wood, 1860-1951.; Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.; Burrows, Julius C. (Julius Caesar), 1837-1915.; Burton, Clarence Monroe, 1853-1932.; Burton, Marion Le Roy, 1874-1925.; Cady, Burt D., 1874-; Carnegie, Andrew, 1835-1919.; Cook, William Randolph, 1866-1946.; Cooper, Harry D., 1863-1933.; Couzens, James, 1872-1936.; Cramton, Louis C. (Louis Convers), b. 1875.; Davidson, James Edward, 1867-; DeFoe, Murl Holcomb, 1879-; Denby, Edwin, 1870-1929.; Dickie, Samuel, 1851-1925.; Dickinson, Luren Dudley, 1859-1943.; Diekema, Gerrit John, 1859-1930.; Dillman, Grover C. (Grover Cleveland), 1889-1979; Fellows, Grant, 1865-1929.; Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.; Ferry, Dexter Mason, 1833-1907.; Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.; Fordney, Joseph W. (Joseph Warren), 1853-1932.; Foulkes, George Ernest, 1878-1960.; Fuller, George N. (George Newman), 1873-1957.; Fuller, Oramel B., b. 1858.; Glasgow, Cassius L., b. 1859.; Gore, Victor M.; Green, Fred W. (Fred Warren), 1872-1936.; Groesbeck, Alexander J. (Alexander Joseph), 1873-1953.; Hamilton, Edward LaRue, 1857-1923.; Hays, Will H. (Will Harrison), 1879-1954.; Hitchcock, Frank H. (Frank Harris), 1867-1935.; Hoffman, Clare Eugene, 1875-1967.; Hudson, Joseph Lowthian, 1846-1912.; Kelley, Patrick Henry, 1867-1925.; Ketcham, John Clark, 1873-1941.; King, Paul H.; Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.; Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.; Landon, Alfred M. (Alfred Mossman), 1887-1987.; Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1890-1961.; McLaughlin, James Campbell, 1858-1932.; McMillan, James, 1838-1902.; Martindale, Frederick C.; Michigan Dry Campaign Committee.; Michigan League for Good Roads.; Michigan Press Association.; Michigan Republican Newspaper Association.; Michigan War Preparedness Board.; Newberry, Truman Handy, 1864-1945.; Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860.; Pattengill, Henry Romaine, 1852-1918.; Patton, John, 1850-1907.; Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946.; Potter, William W., 1869-1940.; Powers, Perry Francis, 1857-1945.; Rich, John Treadway, 1841-1926.; Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.; Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931.; Shafer, Paul W. (Paul Werntz), 1893-1954.; Sigler, Kim, b. 1894.; Sleeper, Albert E., 1862-1934.; Smith, John McMunn C., 1853-1923.; Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.; Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.; Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930.; Thomas, Henry F., 1843-; Townsend, Charles E. (Charles Elroy), 1856-1924.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.; Vaughan, Coleman C., 1857-; Warner, Frederick Maltby, 1865-1923.; Weissert, Charles Adam, 1878-1947.; Wright, Luther Lamphere, 1856-1922.
- Correspondence
  - Undated (Box 1)
  - October 3, 1876-June 18, 1891 (Box 1)
  - 1893, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - 1894
    - Personal and Political (Box 1)
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1895, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - 1896, 6 folders (Box 1)
    (include letters from Shirley Smith describing his trip through Europe, June -- August)
  - 1899 (Box 1)
  - 1900, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - 1901
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Personal (Box 1)
    - Political (Box 1)
    - Michigan Press Association (Box 1)
      (William R. Cook was treasurer)
  - 1902
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Personal (Box 1)
    - Political, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Michigan Press Association (Box 1)
  - 1903
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Personal (Box 1)
    - Political (Box 1)
      (include letters concerning local post office patronage and service)
    - Michigan Press Association (Box 1)
  - 1904
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Personal (Box 1)
    - Political (Box 1)
    - Michigan Press Association (Box 1)
  - 1905
    - Business (Box 2)
    - Political (Box 2)
    - Michigan Press Association (Box 2)
  - 1906 (Box 2)
  - 1907
    - Business (Box 2)
    - Church, post office and other civic affairs (Box 2)
    - Personal (Box 2)
    - Political (Box 2)
  - 1908
    - Business (Box 2)
    - Personal (Box 2)
    - Political, 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Local option, church and other civic activities (Box 2)
  - 1909
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Church and civic (Box 2)
    - Michigan Republican Editors Association, 3 folders (Box 2)
      (M.L. Cook was president)
    - Local option campaign and enforcement, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Personal, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Political, 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Michigan Press Association (Box 2)
  - 1910
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Church, school and civic activities, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Local option campaign, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Michigan Republican Editors Association, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Personal, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Political, 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Michigan Press Association (Box 3)
  - 1911
    - Business (Box 3)
    - Personal (Box 3)
    - Political (Box 3)
  - 1912
    - Lumber business and timber purchases (Box 3)
    - Personal (Box 3)
    - Political, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - 1913
    - Business (Box 3)
    - Lumber business (Box 3)
    - Personal (Box 3)
    - Political (Box 3)
  - 1914
    - Business (Box 3)
    - Church, prohibition, Y.M.C.A., other civic activities (Box 3)
    - Lumbers operations (Box 3)
    - Personal, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Political, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - 1915
    - Business (Box 3)
    - Concerning church, Y.M.C.A., prohibition and Albion College (Box 3)
    - Personal (Box 3)
    - Political (Box 3)
    - Lumber operations (Box 3)
  - 1916
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Personal, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Political, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Church and local option (Box 3)
    - Hospital, Y.M.C.A., other civic activities (Box 3)
  - 1917, 3 folders (Box 4)
  - 1918, 4 folders (Box 4)
  - 1919, 6 folders (Box 4)
  - 1920
    - Business and personal, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Salvation Army Drive (Box 4)
      (M. L. Cook was chairman)
  - 1921, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - 1922 (Box 4)
  - 1923 (Box 4)
  - 1924 (Box 4)
  - 1925, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - 1926 (Box 4)
  - 1927 (Box 4)
  - 1928 (Box 4)
  - 1929, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - 1930, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - 1931 (Box 4)
  - 1932, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 1933, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 1934, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 1935, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - 1936, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 1937, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 1938 (Box 5)
  - 1939 (Box 5)
  - 1940, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - 1941 (Box 5)
  - 1942 (Box 5)
  - 1943-1944 (Box 5)
  - 1945-1950 (Box 5)
- Hastings Rotary Club
  (W. R. Cook was secretary)
  - 1930 (Box 5)
  - 1931
    - Minutes and reports (Box 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
  - 1932
    - Minutes and reports (Box 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
  - 1933
    - Minutes and reports (Box 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
  - 1934
    - Minutes and reports (Box 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 5)
  - 1935
    - Minutes and reports (Box 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 6)
  - 1936
    - Minutes and reports (Box 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 6)
  - 1937
    - Minutes and reports (Box 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 6)
  - 1938
    - Minutes and reports (Box 6)
  - 1939
    - Minutes and reports (Box 6)
  - 1940
    - Minutes and reports (Box 6)
  - 1941
    - Minutes and reports (Box 6)
  - 1942
    - Minutes and reports (Box 6)
  - Committees and attendance records 1920-1940 (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous
  - Political articles and a speech, election campaign 1900 (Box 6)
    (include articles on the Grange as an organization and dealing with Trusts)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6)
    (include copies of newspapers and a Hastings publication; also student notebook, 1880 of Marshall Cook, while attending Albion College)
  - Bills and receipts 1906-1941, 12 folders (Box 6)
  - Financial daybook and ledger 1896-1915, 3 volumes (Box 6)
Selective Index to Correspondents
Aitken, David Demerest, 1853-1930.
Apr. 4, 1896
American Press Association.
1893-1894, 1901-1904, 1909
American Protective Tariff League.
July 20, 1896, Sept. 1, 1896
Anti-Saloon League of Michigan.
1908-1910, 1914-1915, 1917-1919
Bliss, Aaron Thomas, 1837-1906.
Apr. 23, 1896, July 21, 1896, July 23, 1896
Blodgett, John Wood, 1860-1951.
Jan. 23, 1904, May and June 1908, Feb. 13, 1924
Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.
Sept. 18, 1930, Sept. 25, 1930, Apr. 21, 1932, June 2, 1932, May 27, 1936, June 1, 1936, June 15, 1936
Burrows, Julius C. (Julius Caesar), 1837-1915.
Feb. 18, 1901, May 12, 1902, 1910
Burton, Clarence Monroe, 1853-1932.
Dec. 24, 1902
Burton, Marion Le Roy, 1874-1925.
Feb. 6, 1923, Feb. 7, 1923
Cady, Burt D., 1874-
Mar. 14, 1919, Jan. 19, 1920, Jan. 27, 1925, Mar. 6, 1925, Jan. 1928
Carnegie, Andrew, 1835-1919.
Oct. 21, 1910, Nov. 16, 1910
Cooper, Harry D., 1863-1933.
1896
Couzens, James, 1872-1936.
May 31, 1919, June 7, 1919
Cramton, Louis C. (Louis Convers), b. 1875.
1909-1910, Jan. 28, 1920
Davidson, James Edward, 1867-
Mar. 4, 1924
DeFoe, Murl Holcomb, 1879-
1910, Aug. 14, 1914, Aug. 6, 1917, Oct. 29, 1918, Dec. 13, 1928, Feb. 2, 1931
Denby, Edwin, 1870-1929.
Nov. 26, 1920, May 26, 1920, May 29, 1920, Feb. 5, 1921
Dickie, Samuel, 1851-1925.
Feb. 1, 1909, 1910, 1911-1920 [scattered throughout]
Dickinson, Luren Dudley, 1859-1943.
July 5, 1907, 1908-1909, Jan. 3, 1910, Jan. 26, 1914, Feb. 4, 1914
Diekema, Gerrit John, 1859-1930.
July 1910, Sept. 21, 1910, Sept. 24, 1910, Oct. 1912
Dillman, Grover Cleveland, 1889-
May 17, 1935, June 5, 1935
Fellows, Grant, 1865-1929.
Apr. 23, 1907, Apr. 25, 1907, May 7, 1907, Jan. 1909, July 25, 1910, Mar. 11, 1915
Ferris, Woodbridge N., 1853-1928.
Feb. 4, 1914, Sept. 14, 1914
Ferry, Dexter Mason, 1833-1907.
1896
Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.
Dec. 18, 1917, Jan. 2, 1918, Sept. 13, 1930, Sept. 17, 1930, Mar. 28, 1932, Mar. 30, 1932, Sept. 5, 1935, Aug. 3, 1936
Fordney, Joseph W. (Joseph Warren), 1853-1932.
Sept. 24, 1910, Oct. 1910, Apr. 10, 1914, Mar. 10, 1915
Foulkes, George Ernest, 1878-1960.
Dec. 15, 1933
Fuller, George N. (George Newman), 1873-1957.
Jan. 9, 1919, Jan. 30, 1919, Jan. 31, 1919
Fuller, Oramel B., b. 1858.
Oct. 21, 1908, July 30, 1910, July 18, 1916, Sept. 1921, Dec. 31, 1921
Glasgow, Cassius L., b. 1859.
Correspondence throughout
Gore, Victor M.
Feb. 12, 1894, Sept. 21, 1896, Oct. 1, 1896, Oct. 4, 1896
Green, Fred Warren, 1872-1936.
Mar. 6, 1925, Sept. 1925, June 1926, Sept. 15, 1926, 1927, Jan. 4, 1928, Feb. 1929, May 7, 1929, July 8, 1929
Groesbeck, Alexander J., 1873-1953.
Oct. 15, 1912, Oct. 22, 1912, Nov. 7, 1912, Mar. 8, 1913, May 1, 1914, Jan. 27, 1922
Hamilton, Edward LaRue, 1857-1923.
1896, 1900-1904, 1906-1910, 1912, 1914, Mar. 30, 1915, 1916-1919, Jan. 28, 1920
Hays, Will H. (Will Harrison), 1879-1954.
Aug. 5, 1918, Nov. 21, 1919
Hitchcock, Frank H. (Frank Harris), 1867-1935.
Mar. 31, 1908, Mar. 5, 1909
Hoffman, Clare Eugene, 1875-1967.
Sept. 23, 1926, May 24, 1935, Aug. 22, 1935, Apr. 28, 1937
Hudson, Joseph Lowthian, 1846-1912.
June 4, 1910, June 6, 1910
Kelley, Patrick Henry, 1867-1925.
May 26, 1909, May 29, 1909, Jan. 1910, July 1910
Ketcham, John Clark, 1873-1941.
Mar. 1906, Oct. 2, 1908, Aug. 2:1909, May 4, 1910, Mar. 1, 1921, Apr. 21, 1921, Nov. 21, 1921, Dec. 20, 1923, Jan. 4, 1924, Mar. 1924, May 7, 1924, Dec. 20, 1926, Jan 9, 1927, Jan, 5, 1928, Mar. 30, 1929, Mar. 1930, Sept. 15, 1930, Jan. 1935, May 22, 1928
King, Paul H.
Nov. 24, 1909, Dec. 1909, 1910, June 1917
Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.
1910
Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.
Jan. 30, 1905, May 4, 1908, July 1908, 1909-1910, Jan. 16, 1911, Jan. 15, 1912, Jan. 2, 1936, Jan. 6, 1936
Landon, Alfred M. (Alfred Mossman), 1887-1987.
Nov. 28, 1936
Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1890-1961.
May 13, 1926, Sept. 13, 1930, Sept. 23, 1932, Oct. 11, 1932
McLaughlin, James Campbell, 1858-1932.
Apr. 6, 1914, Apr. 13, 1914
McMillan, James, 1838-1902.
Nov. 21, 1893, Mar. 13, 1894, Dec. 12, 1895, Mar. 27, 1901, Mar. 24, 1902, May 12, 1902
Martindale, Frederick C.
Sept. 23, 1908, Mar. 26, 1910, Apr. 21, 1914
Michigan Dry Campaign Committee.
Mar. 1, 1916, Apr. 20, 1916, June 5, 1916
Michigan League for Good Roads.
1896
Michigan Press Association.
1895-1896, 1901-1911
Michigan Republican Editorial Association.
1908-1910
Michigan Republican Newspaper Association.
1895-1896, 1900
Michigan War Preparedness Board.
Aug. 6, 1917, Feb. 21, 1919, Apr. 17, 1919, May 10, 1919, May 23, 1919
Newberry, Truman Handy, 1864-1945.
Dec. 12, 1918, Dec. 13, 1918
Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860
Oct. 1895, 1896, May 1908, July 3, 1908, Nov. 1909, 1910, Jan. 16, 1911, July 5, 1911, Sept. 1914, Oct. 2, 1914, Jan. 23, 1918, July 9, 1930, June 20, 1936, July 14, 1936, Nov. 4, 1939, Dec. 1, 1939, Jan. 23, 1940, Oct. 27, 1943, June 29, 1944, July 15, 1944, Aug. 5, 1944, Sept. 9, 1944
Pattengill, Henry Romaine, 1852-1918.
July 13, 1896
Patton, John, 1850-1907.
June 27, 1902
Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946.
Dec. 6, 1909 [enclosed with letter, Dec. 10, 1909, from Hamilton to Cook]
Potter, William W., 1869-1940.
1909, Oct. 1, 1926, Mar. 1927, Dec. 27, 1927, Jan., Feb. and Nov. 1928, Jan. 17, 1929, Apr. 1930, May 12, 1930
Powers, Perry Francis, 1857-1945.
Aug. 9, 1895, June 30, 1896, Apr. 30, 1900, Nov. 17, 1900, Oct. 17, 1901, Dec. 18, 1901, Nov. 7, 1902, Sept. 1904, June 23, 1907, July 1907, 1909-1910, 1914
Rich, John Treadway, 1841-1926.
June 15, 1894, July 7, 1896, May 9, 1902
Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.
May 4, 1936
Sawyer, Walter H. (Walter Hulme), 1861-1931.
Jan. 25, 1905
Shafer, Paul W. (Paul Werntz), 1893-1954.
Sept. 18, 1943
Sigler, Kim, b. 1894.
Dec. 20, 1930, May 1931, Dec. 1932, Jan. 14, 1933, July 21, 1933, Sept. 1933, Jan. 5, 1934, Apr. 5, 1934, May 18, 1934, Feb. 1935, Mar. 1935, Mar. 27, 1936, Aug. 30, 1939, Nov. 15, 1939, Dec. 28, 1931, Apr. 22, 1936, Aug. 20, 1943, Dec. 29, 1943, May 9, 1944
Sleeper, Albert E., 1862-1934.
Nov. 4, 1908, Feb. 11, 1916, Jan. 1918, June 3, 1919, June 7, 1919, Nov. 14, 1919
Smith, John McMunn C., 1853-1923.
July 1907, Aug. 21, 1907, Aug. 28, 1909, Apr. 1910, Sept. 8, 1910, Sept. 7, 1910, Sept. 21, 1914
Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.
Correspondence throughout
Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.
July 3, 1896, Apr. 1907, May 1, 1907, May 4, 1907, July 15, 1907, Apr. 5, 1909, Aug. 25, 1908, Aug. 29, 1908, Jan. 28, 1910, Apr. 1910, May 2, 1910, June 4, 1910, Nov. 1912, Mar. 1913, Mar. 7, 1914, Apr. 4, 1914, Sept. 4, 1914, Mar. 5, 1915, June 12, 1915, July 25, 1916, May 24, 1917
Taft, William H. (William Howard), 1857-1930.
Aug. 17, 1909 [enclosed with letter, Apr. 25, 1910, from W.A. Smith to Cook]
Thomas, Henry F., 1843-
Mar. 14, 1894, Apr. 11, 1896, May 1, 1896
Townsend, Charles E. (Charles Elroy), 1856-1924.
July 1907, 1908-1910, Feb. 2, 1912, 1913-1915, Dec. 26, 1916, May 1917, June 20, 1918, Mar. 1919, Aug. 16, 1919, Dec. 27, 1921
Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
Oct. 7, 1910, Oct. 19, 1912, Mar. 27, 1914, Nov. 3, 1933, Apr. and May 1934, May 25, 1935, Aug. 1935, Feb. 5, 1936, Apr. 13, 1937, Apr. 16, 1937, Nov. 13, 1939, Nov. 15, 1939
Vaughan, Coleman C., 1857-
May 16, 1896, 1902, Nov. 28, 1903, Dec. 1903, Apr. 1904, Feb. 11, 1905, Feb. 1, 1907, Jan. 30, 1908, Feb. 7, 1908, 1909-1910, Apr. 21, 1913, Jan. 8, 1914, Aug. 14, 1914, Sept. 11, 1914, Jan. 8, 1915, Feb. 5, 1916, Jan. 1919, Aug. 23, 1919, Oct. 23, 1919, 1920, Jan. 21, 1921, July 1924, Sept. 11, 1925, Mar. 17, 1934, Apr. 2, 1934, May 12, 1934
Warner, Frederick Maltby, 1865-1923.
Dec. 29, 1900, Sept. 17, 1902, Feb. 11, 1904, Sept. 13, 1904, Jan. 29, 1907, July 1907, Nov. 2, 1908, Jan. 7, 1909, Jan. 12, 1909 [enclosed with letter, Jan. 13, 1909, from Cook to C.S. Palmerton], June 30, 1920
Weissert, Charles Adam, 1878-1947.
May 8, 1900, June 7, 1900, May 24, 1919, July 18, 1919
Wright, Luther Lamphere, 1856-1922.
Feb. 5, 1909, Feb. 8, 1909, Feb. 15, 1909
Related Material
The library also has the records of the Cook Brothers Printing Company of Hastings, Michigan.